Building
your
online
business?
Go
to
wicks.com
and
set
up
your
store
on
a
single
integrated
platform.
Add
products.
Showcase
them
dynamically.
And
seamlessly
track
your
inventory.
Accept
multiple
secure
payments
and
design
your
storefront
down
to
the
very
last
detail.
Get
all
the
tools
you
need.
Drive
more
sales
with
customizable
gift
cards
and
flexible
products
subscriptions.
Retain
customers
with
a
point-based
loyalty
program.
Email
automations
and
reach
millions
with
sales
channel
integrations.
Complete
your
setup
with
a
personalized
analytics
dashboard.
Make
smart
business
decisions
and
shape
the
next
phase
of
your
business.
Build,
manage
and
grow
from
one
place.
Go
to
wicks
and
launch
your
online
business
today.